<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[NGA]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[NGA]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/nga/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 13:32:08 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/nga/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Big Business: Here’s how you can respect youth and it’s important...]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Big Business: Here’s how you can respect youth and it’s important...</h1><p>Lonely Planet's Japan, Kyoto and Discover Japan guide author Chris Rowthorn, a longtime Kyoto resident who founded Inside Kyoto, has now tackled the city that plays muse to many all over the world: Tokyo. Truly Tokyo is a new online guide, entirely written by Rowthorn himself, that services first-timers and regular visitors.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/b1f4e753c172a0c144b9bcc02d927a0746bed205.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coolhunting.com/travel/truly-tokyo-online-travel-guide</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5375583c-3805-4564-ab32-0ff72d95003a</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 13:32:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Facebook has been redesigned for profit: and teen suicide is a consequence. ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Facebook has been redesigned for profit: and teen suicide is a consequence. </h1><p> In the internet age, the connection between youth suicide and social media is indisputable. In the past decade alone there have been a handful of high-profile cyberbullicides--a term coined by researchers at the Cyberbullying Research Center to describe suicides directly or indirectly caused by cyberbullying. Tragically, a number of these suicides have been filmed or even streamed live on the internet: In 2008, Abraham Biggs, a community college student from Florida posted a suicide note to BodyBuilding.com before broadcasting his suicide over the now-defunct live-streaming website Justin.tv. His peers responded with anything but compassion; instead, some watchers encouraged him to “do it for real”; that is to take the lethal dose of medications he’d concocted, none of the viewers watching called the police until he was already unconscious. </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/ac49eb0380eb5ce40446c86676577665f94fc953.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.thrillist.com/tech/nation/airbnb-hacks-how-to-find-better-cheaper-listings/travel</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6625d03a-33bf-4695-b541-0f4ea8577df6</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 13:25:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>